<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | DCS 210</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>©2022</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/laurie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/laurie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Laurie Baker and my pronouns are she/her. I am a Visiting Assistant Professor in Digital and Computation Studies at Bates College. My research focuses on spatial and temporal patterns in human and biological systems, including disease spread, animal movement, and economic activities such as fishing and shipping. I use spatiotemporal modelling and other data science techniques to understand these patterns and to evaluate the impact of interventions and policy decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My work also focuses on the development of open-source materials that lower barriers to data science education and equip communities with the tools to engage in data science work so that they can address issues of local importance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn to explore, visualize, and analyze data to understand natural phenomena, investigate patterns, model outcomes, and make predictions. Gain insight from data, reproducibly (with literate programming and version control) and collaboratively, using modern programming tools and techniques. The course will focus on the R statistical computing language and assumes no statistical or computing background.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
